They say we're cursed
children because at birth
we possess the power to
control magical beasts.
You worthless disgusting rats
I once heard that a long time
ago it was an ability that only
controlled livestock but then
someone started using it to
command monsters in the war and
as a result killed a bunch of
people so we became loathed!
I told you not to look at
me with those dead eyes!
We were hit, kicked!
Physical abuse became a daily occurrence.
Why do you beat me?
I'll tell you when you can speak
When I asked a question,
I was beaten until I was
almost unrecognizable,
and my food rations were taken
away for three whole days.
Also,
because of the cursed power, I was able
to read the minds of the people around me.
So that thing is demon folk.
I bet it's the one who killed my brother!
Probably planning a way to
exterminate all us humans.
I'm furious.
It should have been that best.
And when they found out that
I could read their minds?
It got worse.
It got even more violent.
It can read minds?
How dreadful.
This is exactly why they can't be trusted!
Disgusting vermin.
I'll just need to die.
But no matter what awful things
happened to me, I never retaliated.
I never even thought of doing so.
Even though I hated that
I was feared, despised,
and attacked, I never
tried to nor wanted to.
Hurt anyone more than anything.
I just didn't want to see any more blood.
However,
you have the power to help make a difference
just by taking these monsters with you.
Demon folk can be useful to
people to the whole nation.
What could bring you more pride?
I can be useful to people if you
simply do what I tell you to do.
You will never be beaten again.
I promise you.
And you will be fed only the finest foods
and not just you—that
goes for everyone else.
Here as well.
But if you refuse, then
you're right back at it.
Unless of course things were
to get even worse for you.
The master wore a magical
device on his forehead,
so I couldn't read his mind.
But he
was a man who always kept his word. So.
so
I trusted him.
He had never lied to me.
I have to kill them all.
The seal.
I can't control it anymore.
I messed up.
No.
Everyone's going to suffer again
because of me because of me.
Okay now it can just
kill me I may not have
helped anyone but I
didn't hurt anyone either.
And that's enough I can die here.
And if I'm to be reborn,
I only hope I won't have to spend
that life with so much suffering.
I hope I can be at least a
little more useful to someone.
And I hope I can have something
delicious to eat at least once.
Life doesn't have to be this way.
Peri!
Why is this person protecting me?
Ah, no! No!
The bleeding stopped.
Come on, come on!
Okay, then.
I think I can make this
work out after all.
Mom, Dad, I'm going to go
gather ingredients for the day.
It all started a short
while after I returned
from the training schools
in the Royal Capital.
It was dinner time.
I got a whole lot this time!
These will be great to dry out in the sun.
And then I can pickle these.
And let me see.
I guess I'll stick these in a soup.
Mmm, hey, that's pretty good.
Even if there was something
disgusting in there,
I thought it would just give
me a bit of a stomach ache.
But it was highly poisonous.
Bad idea.
Low heel.
This is it.
Dragon's Ruin.
Mom had always told me
never to eat this one.
How could I have forgotten that?
I still have work to do.
Low heel.
Well, that's weird.
I'm feeling better.
But I'm still hungry.
Dragon's Ruin I have to be careful.
A poison spike.
I think it's.
It's.
It was also highly poisonous.
I don't know why.
But I'm feeling okay.
If I can survive.
Eating poison maybe I can eat this too.
I don't believe it.
This actually tastes.
Really good.
huh.
The poison is spreading
slower than yesterday.
I'm gaining some. Tolerance.
All right.
This might mean that I'm
starting to get a new ability.
This?
is awesome!
From that moment on, I developed
a taste for poisonous things.
On occasion, I collapsed, and in the
end, I didn't acquire any skills.
But, I could eat poisonous things
without dying, only some
vomiting and a little blood.
Oh man, I love it! I can't believe
that poisonous creatures
are this delicious!
Oh, who even knew?
And that's probably why.
This isn't hitting me too hard.
Instructor!
At first, I couldn't counteract the
poison, so I coughed up some blood.
But I know from experience,
that much is no big deal.
Is the kid okay?
My low-heal detox seems
to have taken effect.
Harry!
Wow.
How can you take on such a
horrible creature all by himself?
Perry!
Oh, man.
I guess this is it.
It's about to give it one last shot.
But...
Perry!
This stench is awful. Dear God.
Strange that such a huge and dangerous
frog is just outside the city.
But, well, for me, I bet this big
fella is probably pretty tasty.
Oh, are you all right?
I'm fine.
Nah, he's not looking too good.
I should probably have
Lin give him a look over.
That really was a close one, kid.
Are you out here all by yourself?
No, sir. I am.
I was the one.
Hmm?
I'm the one who brought that thing here.
Um, because I promised
to bring it to the city.
He was bringing it to the city?
And why would he promise to do that?
And promise who?
Wait, he can't mean...
That has to be it.
That frog must be for a giant feast.
And actually,
if you're trying to deliver
that much fresh meat,
Getting it there while still alive
is the best way to do it for sure.
Now I understand why he had
to use a seal to hide himself,
to be safe and not get robbed. Plus,
I'm sure a city that large would have the
techniques to manage
such a poison properly.
And you know what?
I bet this kid even
put in all the time and
effort to raise this frog from the start.
Grow up strong and healthy.
Good boy, that's it.
Get a good jump in.
You're doing great.
Ah, I'm the worst.
I ruined the delivery of
his precious livestock.
I'm sorry I messed everything up.
I'm not sure what this is
worth, but I'll pay for it.
I don't have much money on me right now,
so you know it's going
to take me some time.
No, wait a second.
You don't have to pay for it.
But...
It's really okay. Don't worry.
Wait, no. Are you sure?
But it's in so many pieces now.
No, it's fine, really.
Okay, then.
So, how did you even get that
creature this far anyway?
I can't imagine you could
have dragged it here.
Well, um, I can control monsters.
That's how I was able to
bring it all the way here.
What do you mean you can control them?
That's incredible.
This tiny kid can really
manipulate something that enormous?
Kid, it's mind-boggling.
Are there other people in the
world who have that skill?
Huh? Skill?
Is it not one?
I was born with it, so it's
just something I can do. Hmm.
You say you were born with it,
so you've been able to do that
since you can remember, huh?
That's impressive, kid.
A remarkable gift like that can only be
sent down from the gods in the heavens.
Well, I, um, you see, I'm...
I'm demon folk.
Demon folk?
Yeah.
All demon folk can do that sort of thing.
Ah, okay,
so I would have to assume that demon folk
are a people who all possess that ability,
and it's nothing really
special for you. Yeah.
I've imagined so many times about
what I'd do if I had that skill.
I'd have animals help
work the fields and stuff.
And if I could use birds, it'd be
nice to have them deliver letters.
At night, I wouldn't have to worry
about getting attacked by stray dogs.
I mean it.
I'm kind of jealous.
Um, so then you're not
afraid of the demon folk?
You don't hate me for what I can do?
What do you mean?
There are a lot of
people out there who are
scared of my power and
really hate that I have it.
Who on earth would hate
a cool power like that?
For real, I don't think you
should pay much mind to them.
Those fools can say what they want,
but that's a super useful ability.
Useful.
Me? Really? Of course.
That's what I've been trying
to tell you, my friend.
It's great.
I wish I could take it off your hands.
Really?
Can someone like me really be
needed and considered helpful?
Do you really mean it?
Unlike me,
this kid was blessed
with a desirable ability,
so why does he have so little self-worth?
He probably has plenty to deal with right
now, but I'm sure he's going places.
Telling you, buddy, your
talent is a wonderful thing.
People need that way
more than they need me.
Instructor, are you all right?
Yeah, completely fine.
I must treat you immediately.
No need.
I'm really okay now.
I'm not even bleeding.
Not to brag, but I'm
strong against poison.
You would have to be that.
Wasn't just any poison.
That was a miasma.
I'm sure of it.
an extreme toxin that
even ruins the very soil.
He took a direct attack and then
carried on like it was nothing.
Wait, there is one possibility.
Sacred Spirit.
Instructor Sane the Sovereign
of Salvation once showed it
to me by honing the body and
mind like a reverend saint.
This technique purifies everything
it touches and heals all wounds.
It is the perfection he found at the end
of his rather unconventional training.
It took Instructor Sane 40 years,
but Nora has managed to
achieve it while still young.
Oh yeah, Lin.
Why don't you take care of this kid first?
I'm fine.
I don't need help, thank you.
Pale skin.
Hair of silver mixed with light blue.
Dark eyes that seem like they're
pulling you into their depths.
It must be.
Are you a demon folk?
Yeah, demon folk.
You know your stuff.
Yes, well, Instructor, this child,
um, what are you planning to do?
If I can, I want to take
him in the carriage.
Sir Noor, you can't. What? Why not?
They are a dangerous race.
Most countries immediately
exterminate them.
You really okay with that, Instructor?
This child is demon folk, and the
monster it brought caused all this.
It sure is unfortunate that
the weed field got destroyed,
but he can't finish his job with
the poison frog because of me.
I feel bad.
Do you mean the Black Death Dragon?
You were bringing that to the city?
He's just a child, but he must
know how dangerous that is.
So you promised someone to bring
the Black Death Dragon with you.
Who asked you to do that?
I don't really know.
They wouldn't tell me who it was.
Concealing the truth will do you no good.
It is very important that
you tell us what you know.
I really don't know who they are.
I'm sorry.
This is just the way it seems to work.
His frightened demeanor and the
look in his eyes, it's clear as day.
This child is a slave.
Slaves are outlawed
within the Clay's kingdom,
but that isn't the case in some places.
Because in all likelihood,
he's a child soldier whose status
is being taken advantage of.
Do you have a place you call home?
I'm afraid I was blindfolded
part of the way here.
I wouldn't even know how to start
going back to where I came from.
Okay, then what do you
think about this idea?
I would like to give him a
ride to the nearest city.
What was I thinking?
My father often warned me
not to be misled by rumors
and to trust my own eyes when
passing judgment on others.
But from the moment we met him,
I only saw a boy from a wicked race
that I had always been taught to fear.
I didn't see him as a malnourished child
with thin legs and arms and no place to go.
I'm ashamed of myself for
being so small-minded.
Now then, what's your name?
Rolo. Oh yeah?
That's a great name.
It'll be easy to remember.
Ines, I have a favor to ask of you.
Can we take this child?
Can we bring Rolo with us?
Lady, please.
I know how you feel. However...
If there's no room, he can have my spot.
That is not the problem, okay?
The demon folk are not allowed entry into
Mithra, which is our ultimate destination.
It would be difficult
to bring him with us.
Of course, by the same token, if we
were to leave him on the way there,
it would be difficult
for him to survive alone.
She's not wrong.
And if we bring him with us, we may be
considered enemies of Mithra and attacked.
Even so, I...
This is unexpected.
Interesting.
I guess I made a mistake in assuming
it would have been long dead by now.
Kevin
The. The.
I don't have to give a chance.
I will give a light for my response.
I will give a light to light.
I don't have to say anything.
I'll be right back to you.
Give me love.